arup.com 2009-06-22

# Privacy policy | Arup

**Data storage**

We collect the domain and IP address of all visitors to the Arup site. This information does not identify you as an individual, but only the computer that is being used to view the site. The data is used for statistical analysis to help us improve our service to you. We do not link this data with any personal information collected through the site (see data collection and use). We also use cookies on the Arup website for statistical analysis.

 **Data collection and use**

On occasion, you will be asked to submit personal information about yourself (eg name and e-mail address etc) in order to receive or use services via our website. Such services include job enquiries and requests for information about Arup’s work.

By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable Arup to provide you with the services you select. Whenever you provide such personal information, we will treat that information in accordance with this policy. Any information you provide will never be supplied to anyone outside Arup without first obtaining your consent, unless we are obliged or permitted by law to disclose it.

We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the service you have requested, and remove it in the event that the purpose has been met. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in accordance with relevant data protection legislation.

 **Access to your personal data**

To enquire about accessing your personal data, or if you have any questions relating to Arup's data privacy policy, please contact: Farrukh Ahmed (Data Protection Officer), 13 Fitzroy Street, London, UK, W1T 4BQ.

Please note that we charge a £10/US$15 administration fee for information requests.
